Curriculum Vitae

SUMMARY

I had studied programming while in college, and decided to further develop my programming skills, join many programming bootcamps Frontend and Backend, especially in web programming. I have over 1 working years of experience as an Frontend Developer and passion for clean code & solve problem with code. I hope my knowledge I have learned so far can be useful for the future

INFORMATION

Full Name : Akhsan Bayu Riantama

Place, Date of Birth : Jayapura, 3 February 1999

Gender : Male

Address : Jl. Kopeng KM 5, Tegalrejo, Magelang

Email : akhsanby@gmail.com

Phone Number : +62895401224170

EDUCATION

STMIK Bina Patria, Kota Magelang - S.Kom

October 2017 - Desember 2021

Graduate as Informatics Engineering student with GPA 3.49 by produce a final assignment about step prediction with AI

WORKING EXPERIENCE

| Digireg Indonesia - Frontend Developer |
|----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------|
| March 2022 – February 2023 |
| ☐ Create a WebGIS frontend based on wireframes specified by the client or company |
| ☐ Collaborate with Backend Developers in creating APIs to create response need of |
| Frontend Developer |
| \square Revise and create website-based company supporting tools according to compan |
| requests |

EXPERTISE AND SKILLS

Programing Language

PHP, Javascript

Framework / Library

Laravel, VueJS, ReactJS, ExpressJS

Design Tools

Inkscape, Figma

TRAINING & COURSE

Course Coding Online in Dicoding Academy

2020 - 2021

| Learn the basics of HTML and CSS as the pillars of a website. Learn the basics of JavaScript, from the fundamentals, syntax and features of ES6, to the concept of automation tests using popular frameworks. Learn a lot & deeply about JavaScript to make website attractive. |
|---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------|
| Course Coding Online in Udemy |
| 2023 - Present |
| Im currently studying Golang : Beginner to Advanced, Laravel : Beginner to Advanced, & NodeJS : Beginner to Advanced with Programmer Zaman Now |
| Kampus Merdeka with Hacktiv8 |
| August 2021 – February 2022 |
| ☐ I learn basic HTML & Css in Kode.id |
| ☐ I learn Javascript ES6 : Basic to Advance in Kode.id |
| ☐ I lean Styling Component ReactJS in Kode.id |
| ☐ I learn how to use ReactJS & React Native with reusable components & write clean code in Kode.id |
| ☐ I learn how to use state management Redux with best practice in Kode.id |

SOCIAL MEDIA

Github - https://github.com/akhsanby

Portfolio web - https://akhsanby.my.id

Linkedin - https://www.linkedin.com/in/akhsanby